

Sineenart Borriboon (Nane)

Date of birth: 26 April 1997 Address: Bangkok, Thailand E-mail: Sineenartbrr@gmail.com

Tel: 085 -366-4730

2 years experience in Key account and administrator positions in E-commerce, Robotic and Fashion companies . Familiar with e-commerce platforms demonstrated skills in communicating, managing platforms for clients, and maintaining a good relationship with clients.

Educational History

Silpakorn University

Management and Science BBA in Business management and English since 2018

Skills

- Basic Microsoft office including Word, Basic excel and Powerpoint
- Shopee and Facebook Ads optimization
- Photoshop editing skills
- Good at English
- Team player
- Multitasking

Work Experience

True Digital Co.Ltd (May 2021 - Present)

Sales Administrator

- Coordinating with the other departments, clients, and vendors outside the org.
- Monitoring and managing robot transportation schedules
- Reserving a van for sales staff (in case of robot deployment)
- Responsible for issuing disbursement within the team
- Receiving, creating, and collecting any sales documents.
- Supporting sales
- Any assignment from the manager

Shopee Thailand Co.,Ltd (June 2020 – March 2021)

Key Account Management (Shop management agent)

- Monitoring and communicating with seller users in the FMCG category
- Convincing and dealing seller users to join every essentials campaign
- Consulting every basic service on a platform
- Building and maintaining a relationship with seller users
- Negotiating and advising products setting prices in the FMCG category
- Managing seller user's budgets to make product rebated
- Offering Shopee's essentials advertise for seller users
- Monitoring and managing over 100 stores on Shopee platform
- Solving and handling delivery issues between seller users and partner shipping companies
- Decorating shops on Shopee platform
- Editing product photos for seller users

Pat Luxury Concept Co.,Ltd (2020 – June2020)

Secretary and administrator

- Welcoming visitors
- Purchasing and storing an office equipment
- Applying visa for CEO
- Preparing and managing CEO's personal documents
- Preparing necessary equipment to staff for making brand promotions events
- Answering customers lines
- · Any works assignment

Human resource executive

- Checking and recording the absence of employees
- Checking the overtime and time roster plans of brand area staff
- Checking and calculating staff's grooming and incentive rates from every brand under the company
- · Training internship
- Providing and dealing with temporary part-time staff for brand promotion events
- Making an employment contracts for temporary staff
- Making a withholding tax report for temporary staff
- Notifying and applying employees health insurance

Internship

AFS Thailand May 2019 - July 2019

- Training in a Administrators department
- Support other department

Activities

- Culture exchange student program at Daejeon University Korea (2018)
- International Camp including Thai, Korean, Vietnam, Taiwan and Brunei students (2018-2019)
- Main MC Music club (2018-2019)